

PROFILE

I am a UX/UI Designer with more than 5 years of experience conceptualizing and crafting digital products helping businesses and non-profits expand their capacity for impact. I love working on complex UX problems and finding opportunity for good user experience and surpass client expectations.

EXPERIENCE

Sr. Graphic & UI/UX Designer

Sep 2022 - Present

INFIAPP SOLUTION PVT.LTD.

I am playing the role of a senior graphic designer and team Leader. I am a part of making an application which is based on Canva. Graphic Designers create visual concepts with the goal of attracting the interest of clients through digital and physical designs that typically use graphics, images, art, and other visual elements. Although Graphic Designers may use a variety of tools to create their designs, all Graphic Designers must be able to use their hands at least occasionally to create designs, even if they prefer to rely on their digital skills and graphic design software.

Sr. UI/UX Designer

MAY 2019 - AUG 2022

DEVKRUSHNA INFOTECH PVT. LTD.

Working as a Product Designer and UX/UI Designer to create cutting edge User Experience for Products from scratch. My role include understanding the Target Audience, following the **User Centered**Design(UCD) Process, ideate the UJM(User Journey Map) for optimal user interactions, conceptualize Topographical contents, Brainstorming ideas about the featured products, Wireframing Screens, Prototyping the final product to give Proper Product Presentation, create Marketing new Contents Video Contents etc.

Also worked as a Lead ANDROID & IOS APP Designer, role include complete Ideation of the App, Screen-short Concepts, Design UX/UI, making Game Ready etc..

Jr. Graphics Designer

March 2018 - Feb 2019

KMPHITECH INFOTECH

Here my role was to create concept-based app design and app material Graphic Designers create visual concepts with the goal of attracting the interest of clients through digital and physical designs that typically use graphics, images, art, and other visual elements.

Web / Graphics Designer

Aug 2017 - Feb 2018

13 INFOTCH

I served as an employee in I3 Info-tech, and I also used to give lectures on web designing to MCA students.



+91 78744-22137



+9178744-22137



nilamthavani78@mail.com



/Thavani Nilam/

EDUCATION

Year 2015 - 2017

Bachelor of Commerce (B.com)

J. Z. SHAH ARTS & H. P. DESAI COMMERCE COLLEGE

Year 2016 - 2017

Web Designing

RED AND WHITE MULTIMEDIA EDUCATION

SKILLS

PROFESSIONAL

- UX/UI Layouts
- · Low & High Fidelity Designs
- Prototyping
- · User Centric Design
- · App & Games Content Design
- Video Editing

TECHNICAL

- Photoshop
- Illustrator
- After Effects
- Media Encoder
- JSON Lottie
- HTML/CSS
- Javascripe
- Bootstrap
- Media Query

LANGUAGE

English

Gujarati

Hindi